<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Bike Lock</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">The Bike lock</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">En cours de dev</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_app_bar">About</string>
    <string name="button_text">Unlock</string>
    <string name="unlock_string">Nfc code does not work ...</string>
    <string name="about_unlock">
        <b>Activating NFC</b>
        \n\nIf your device has NFC, the chip and Android Beam need to be activated so that you can use NFC:\n\n
        1. Go to Settings > More.\n\n
        2. Tap on the NFC switch to activate it. The Android Beam function will also automatically turn on.\n\n
        3. If Android Beam does not automatically turn on, just tap it and select Yes to turn it on.\n\n
        Smartphones NFC capabilities operate in tandem with Android Beam. If Android Beam is disabled, it may limit NFC’s sharing capacity.
    </string>
    <string name="about_string">
        <b>CONFIDENTIALITE\n\n</b>La présente application est la propriété de Rémi Meunier, Pierre Pavlovic et Henri Pineau, avec la société ESEO.
        Elle est diffusé pour les seuls besoins du PFE. Il ne doit pas être reproduit, entièrement ou partiellement, ou
        employé pour tout autre but sans autorisation écrite préalable de Henri Pineau, et à la condition que cette notification soit
        incluse dans une telle reproduction. Aucune information quant au contenu ou aux thèmes de ce document ne
        peut être communiquée de quelque façon à un tiers sans autorisation écrite de Henri Pineau.\n\nL’équipe de consultants du PFE échappe à ces restrictions et peut utiliser la présente
        application pour toute utilisation qui leur convient, et ce sans autorisation de Henri Pineau. \n \n \n

        <b>DESCRIPTION\n\n</b>Antivol de cadre pour vélo connecté. Réalisation antivol de vélo connecté à une application
        sur smartphone. Fonctionnant en bluetooth et intégrant une géolocalisation en temp réel et un protocole
        de communication tel que LoRa ou SIGFOX. De plus l ouverture et la fermeture seront automatisées grâce
        à un moteur intégré.\n\n\n

        <b>LICENSE\n\n</b>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE\nVersion 3, 29 June 2007\nCopyright 2018 Rémi Meunier, Pierre Pavlovic et Henri Pineau\n\nThis program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.\n\nThis program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.\n\nYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see https://www.gnu.org/licenses/\n\n\n

        © Pierre Pavlovic\n\n\n

    </string>

</resources>
